Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
- Box: 25, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Estimated Number of Wage and Salary Workers in Nonagricultural Establishments, 1965; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
    Author: Division of Labor Statistics and Research
  - Item 7: Estimated Number of Wage and Salary Workers in Nonagricultural Establishments, 1965; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Estimated Number of Wage and Salary Workers in Nonagricultural Establishments, 1965; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: California Manufacturing Employment at Mid-Decade, 1965; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: Estimated Number of Wage and Salary Workers in Nonagricultural Establishments, 1968; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Box: 25, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Fuller Employment?, 1965; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Author: M. J. Farrell
  - Item 2: Trade Unions and Full Employment, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Author: Conservative Party
  - Item 3: Fuller Employment?, 1965; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Author: M.J.Farrell
  - Item 4: Trade Unions and Full Employment, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Box: 25, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Employment Population and Housing on Oahu, 1970; Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
    Author: The Hawaiian Electric Company
  - Item 2: Employment Population and Housing, 1970; Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
    Notes: 1951-1970
- Box: 25, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Indiana State Employment Service, 1963; Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Author: Indiana Employment Security Division
    Notes: October 15, 1963
  - Item 2: Indiana State Employment Service, 1963; Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Box: 25, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Civilian Workforce, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Author: Kansas Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Statewide Employment Statistics, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area Wichita, KS, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Kansas Segment of the Kansas City Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Statewide Civilian Workforce, 1963; Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Statewide Employment Statistics, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Author: Kansas State Employment Service
  - Item 8: Kansas Segment of the Kansas City Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Box: 25, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Kentucky Employment Trends from 1951 to 1963 with Projections to 1965-75, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
    Author: University of Kentucky
  - Item 2: Kentucky Employment Trends from 1951 to 1963 with Projections to 1965-75, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Box: 25, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Employment Trends in Louisiana, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
    Author: Kyou E. Choi
  - Item 2: Employment Trends in Louisiana, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Box: 25, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: How to Register Ideas Through the Employee Publication, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
    Notes: September 1953
  - Item 2: How to Register Ideas through the Employee Publication, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Box: 25, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Revised Annual Summaries of Nonagricultural Employment, 1969; Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
    Author: Maine Employment Security Commission
    Notes: February 19, 1969
  - Item 2: Revised Annual Summaries of Nonagricultural Employment 1964 and 1965, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
    Notes: February 11, 1966
  - Item 3: Revised Annual Summaries of Nonagricultural Employment, 1969; Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
    Notes: February 18, 1969
  - Item 4: Revised Annual Summaries of Nonagricultural Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Box: 25, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employment Trends in Michigan's Upper Peninsula, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
    Author: Michigan State University
  - Item 2: Employment Trends in Michigan's Upper Peninsula, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
    Author: David G. Greene
    Notes: January 1961
- Box: 25, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Employment and Earnings in the Upper Midwest: 1950-1960, 1962; Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Employment and Earnings in the Upper Midwest, 1962; Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Box: 25, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Manpower Horizons '75, 1968; Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
    Author: State of Nevada
    Notes: July 1968
  - Item 2: Manpower Horizons '75, 1968; Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Box: 25, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: New England Labor and the Economy at the Year-End, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 2: New England Labor and the Economy at the Year-End, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Box: 25, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Industrial Development and Employment Changes in New Hampshire 1950 to 1963, 1964; Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
    Author: Carolyn A. Brackett
    Notes: August 1964
  - Item 2: Industrial Development and Employment Changes in New Hampshire, 1964; Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Box: 25, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Employment Distribution in New York City and its Central Business District, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
    Author: New York City Department of City Planning
    Notes: May 1961
  - Item 2: Employment Opportunities for Minorities in New York City: An Introduction, 1968; Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
    Author: U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission
  - Item 3: Gains in Employment, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
    Author: Abraham C. Burstein
  - Item 4: Employment Distribution in New York City and its Central Business District, 1961; Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 5: Employment Opportunities for Minorities in New York City: An Introduction, 1968; Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: Gains in Employment, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Box: 25, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Changing Employment Patterns in New York State 1950 to 1964, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
    Author: New York State Department of Labor
    Notes: February 1966
  - Item 2: Insured Employment in Selected Countries with Employment of 100,00 or More, 1970; Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
    Notes: March 1970
  - Item 3: Changing Employment Patterns in New York State 1950 to 1964, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: Insured Employment in Selected Counties with Employment of 100,000 or More, 1970; Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Box: 25, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Job Vacancy Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
    Author: U.S. Joint Economic Committee
  - Item 2: Job Vacancy Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Box: 25, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Fluctuation of Employment in Automobile Manufacturing, Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
    Author: Ohio Department of Industrial Relations
  - Item 2: Fluctuation of Employment in Automobile Manufacturing and Related Industries in Ohio, 1930; Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Box: 25, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania Employment the War and After, 1944; Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
    Author: George L. Leffler & Mary Virginia Brown
  - Item 2: Employment by Broad Industry Groups and by County for Selected Years: 1919-1961, 1963; Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
    Author: Pennsylvania Department of Internal Affairs
    Notes: April 1963
  - Item 3: Pennsylvania Employment the War and After, 1944; Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Item 4: Employment Statistics in Pennsylvania for Selected Years, 1963; Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Box: 25, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Employment Multipliers for the Philadelphia Metropolitan Area, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
    Author: James R. Westkott
    Notes: October 1966
  - Item 2: Employment Multipliers for the Philadelphia Metropolitan Area, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Box: 25, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Estimation of Differential Employment Multipliers in a Small Regional Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
    Author: Steven J. Weiss & Edwin C. Gooding
    Notes: November 1966
  - Item 2: Estimation of Differential Employment Multipliers in a Small Regional Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Box: 25, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: National Association of Business Teacher-Training Institutions, 1948; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
    Author: Earl Clevenger
  - Item 2: Selection and Placement, Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 3: Orienting Your New Employee, 1943; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
    Author: U.S. War Department
    Notes: April 1943
  - Item 4: Seleccion de Personal, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
    Author: Departamento de Relaciones Industriales
  - Item 5: Hiring and Firing, 1918; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 6: Selection and Placement of New Employees, 1946; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
    Author: Commonwealth of Australia Department of Labour and National Service
  - Item 7: National Association of Business Teacher-Training Institutions, 1948; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
    Notes: December 1948
  - Item 8: Selection and Placement, Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 9: Orienting Your New Employee, Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 10: Seleccion de Personal, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 11: Hiring and Firing, 1918; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 12: Selection and Placement of New Employees, 1946; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Box: 25, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Comparison of U.S. and U.S.S.R. Employment in Industry, 1963; Publication (Box 25, Folder 48)
    Author: Murray S. Weitzman
    Notes: January 1963
- Box: 25, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: The Chances of Full Employment Considered in Ten Sicilian Villages, Publication (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Box: 26, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Policy for Full Employment, 1960; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress
    Notes: October 24, 1960
  - Item 2: A Guaranteed Employment System in the United States, 1967; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Lewis Schipper
  - Item 3: Controlling Seasonal Slumps, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Coal Miners' Insecurity, 1922; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Russell Sage Foundation
    Notes: April 1922
  - Item 5: Full Employment Objectives in Relation to the Problem of European Co-Operation, 1951; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Council of Europe
  - Item 6: Employment Policy in Norway, 1950; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: The Norwegian Joint Committee on International Social Policy
  - Item 7: Industry's Progress Toward Steady Work and Steady Pay, 1948; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers
  - Item 8: Legislation for Reconversion, 1944; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: U.S. War Contracts Subcommittee
    Notes: December 18, 1944
  - Item 9: Stabilization of Production and Employment, 1945; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Rolf Nugent, Arthur Stone Dewing, Brown Zahniser
    Notes: December 13, 1945
  - Item 10: Report of Committee on Employment and Relief, 1950; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Committee on Employment and Relief
  - Item 11: Employment Regularization, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Can Full Employment be Sustained?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Paul W. McCracken
  - Item 13: Hearings Before the Committee on Labor, 1916; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: U.S. National Employment Bureau
    Notes: February 3, 4, 10, 17, 1916
  - Item 14: Managing a Full Employment Economy, 1966; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Notes: May 1966
  - Item 15: The Impact of the Fiscal System on Local Labor Market Conditions, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Arthur Butler
  - Item 16: Stabilization Policy and Employment, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Andrew F. Brimmer
    Notes: January 10, 1969
  - Item 17: Progress in Stabilizing Factory Employment, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Automobile Manufacturers Association
- Box: 26, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Stabilizing Employment in Baltimore Industries, 1931; Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Author: Municipal Commission on Employment Stabilization
    Notes: May 1931
- Box: 26, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Impact of the Fiscal System on Local Labor Market Conditions, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Box: 26, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employee Displacement: Minimizing its Adverse Effects, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Box: 26, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Estimated Total Nonagricultural Employment in the Memphis, Nashville, Chattanooga and Knoxville Standard Metropolitan Statistical Areas in Tennessee, 1967; Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Author: Tennessee Department of Employee Security
    Notes: October 1967
  - Item 2: Tennessee Employment Statistics, 1967; Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Tennessee Employment Statistics, 1966; Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Tennessee Employment Statistics, 1939-1964, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Box: 26, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Estimated Total Nonagricultural Employment in Chattanooga, Tennessee Area, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Notes: May 1963
- Box: 26, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Structure and Change, 1964; Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Author: Tennessee Valley Authority
    Notes: November 1964
- Box: 26, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Employment in Relation to U.S. Imports, 1960; Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Jobs and Growth, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Author: Conference on Economic Progress
  - Item 3: Investing in Jobs, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Author: U.S. Department of Commerce
  - Item 4: Domestic Employment Attributable to U.S. Exports, 1960; Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Employment in Relation to U.S. Imports, 1960; Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Box: 26, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Investment for Jobs, 1959; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Key Policies for Full Employment, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 1962
  - Item 3: Jobs and Growth, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: National Budgets for Full Employment, 1945; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Author: National Planning Association
    Notes: April 1945
  - Item 5: Public Service Employment Programs: An Opportunity and a Challenge, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Author: Everett Crawford
  - Item 6: Can Government Guarantee Full Employment?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America
  - Item 7: Full Employment, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Author: University of Hawaii
    Notes: November 1963
  - Item 8: Employment Relationship Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1973; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Notes: February 1973
  - Item 9: Manufacturing Employment by State, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Box: 26, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Diversification of Manufacturing Employment for States and Metropolitan Areas, 1960; Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 1960
- Box: 26, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Detecting and Controlling Errors in the BLS Industry Employment Statistics Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Item 2: Measuremtent of Employment, Hours, and Earnings in Nonagricultural Industries, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: New Benchmark Levels for BLS Establishment Employment Estimates, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Notes: September 1963
  - Item 4: Labor Force, Employment, and Unemployment Statistics, 1947-61, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Box: 26, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Vermont Department of Employment Security
- Box: 26, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Employment and Underemployment of Rural People in the Upper Monongahela Valley, West Virginia, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Author: West Virginia University
    Notes: June 1957
  - Item 2: Report of Post-War Employment Committee on Post-War Labor Force, Job Opportunities and Employment, 1945; Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Author: West Virginia State Planning Board
    Notes: December 15, 1945
- Box: 26, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor Force Charts for Wisconsin, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Author: Wisconsin State Employment Service
- Box: 26, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Kerner Commission Report and Economic Policy, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
    Author: Irving H. Siegel
    Notes: January 1969
- Box: 26, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employment Services, 1968; Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Author: Colorado Legislative Council
- Box: 26, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: National Employment Association Directory, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Author: National Employment Association
    Notes: May 1962
- Box: 26, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Employment Agencies, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
    Author: Employment Agents Federation of Great Britain
- Box: 26, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Relating to Employment Bureaus and Labor Agencies, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Author: State of Louisiana
- Box: 26, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Evaluation of Comments on Report on Problems in Filling Job Orders and Placing Job Applicants in Massachusetts, 1975; Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
    Notes: January 23, 1975
  - Item 2: Private Employment Agencies, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
    Author: The Commonwealth of Massachusetts
    Notes: November 13, 1963
- Box: 26, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Survey of Services to Jobseekers, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Author: Alabama Department of Industrial Relations
- Box: 26, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Administration of Public Employment Bureaus, 1915; Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    Author: Walter Lincoln Sears
    Notes: September 2, 1915
- Box: 26, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Public Employment Exchanges, 1914; Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
    Author: The City Club of New York
  - Item 2: Progress in Public Employment Service, 1934; Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
    Author: New York State Employment Service
- Box: 26, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: A Study of Hiring Channels, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
    Author: North Dakota State Employment Service
- Box: 26, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Regulations Governing Operation of Private Employment Agencies, 1964; Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
    Author: Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry
- Box: 26, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Hiring Channels of Employers and Workers in the Spokane, Washington Area, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
    Author: Spokane Local Office and Research and Statistics Section
    Notes: January 1962
- Box: 26, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Potential Savings through Consolidation and Reduction of Certain Employment Service Activities in Wisconsin, 1966; Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Box: 26, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Unemployment: A Problem of Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Author: American Association for Labor Legislation
  - Item 2: Labor Exchanges, 1915; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Interstate Conference of Employment Security Agencies, 1948; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Author: Bi-Regional Conference Report
    Notes: May 3, 4, 5, 1948
  - Item 4: Annual Report of the Alliance Employment Bureau, 1913; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Author: Alliance Employment Bureau
  - Item 5: Community Employment Program Developments in 1961, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: State Laws Regulating Private Employment Agencies, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: A Report of the U.S. Employment Service Task Force, 1965; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. Employment Service Task Force
    Notes: December 23, 1965
  - Item 8: Evaluation of the Concentrated Employment Program, 1968; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Notes: July 11, 1968
  - Item 9: Analysis of the Early Phase Problems of CEP II, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Notes: February 10, 1969
  - Item 10: The Concentrated Employment Program: Issues and Answers, 1970; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Report to the Congress of the United States, 1961; Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    Author: U.S. General Accounting Office
- Box: 26, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Workers' Attitudes and the Acceptability of Shift-Work in New Zealand Manufacturing Industry, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    Author: Stephen Griew and Eileen Philipp
- Box: 26, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Exploring Michigan's Employment Expectations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: Michigan Employment Security Commission
  - Item 2: Methods of Long-Term Projection of Requirements for and Supply of Qualified Manpower, 1967; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: Unesco
  - Item 3: Manpower Directions '75, 1967; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: Arizona State Employment Service
  - Item 4: Survey of the High-Level Manpower Requirements and Resources for the Five-Year Development Plan, 1964-65 to 1968-69, 1965; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: United Republic of Tanzania
  - Item 5: Reflexions on Education, Automation and Long-Term Labor Market Forecasting, 1965; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: National Central Bureau of Statistics
    Language: Swedish; English.
  - Item 6: Brief Summary of S. 2388, Economic Opportunity Act Amendments and Emergency Employment Act, 1967; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare
    Notes: September 13, 1967
  - Item 7: On-the-Job Training in Milwaukee-Nature, Extent, and Relationship to Vocational Education, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    Author: Richard Perlman
  - Item 8: Assessing the Extent of Manpower Forecasting Among Milwaukee Firms, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)